{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/51623314","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51623314","name":"Greektown Casino - Barstool Sports Book","address":"555 Lafayette E.","zipcode":"48226","owner":"Greektown Casino","licenseNumber":"252336","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"150","coords":"-83.04131,42.33457","geojson":{"id":"51623314","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.041311005,42.3345671]},"properties":{"name":"Greektown Casino - Barstool Sports Book","owner":"Greektown Casino","address":"555 Lafayette E.","zipcode":"48226","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"252336","establishmentid":"51623314","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"150","most_recent_license_date":"2022-05-03"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"3831","name":"Greektown Casino - High Limits","address":"555 Lafayette Ave. E.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"3832","name":"Greektown Casino-Shotz","address":"555 LaFayette Ave. E.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"3829","name":"Greektown Casino - Monroe Market","address":"555 Lafayette Ave. E.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"3676","name":"Greektown Casino-Pantheon Club","address":"555 LaFayette Ave. E.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"3677","name":"Greektown Casino-Trappers","address":"555 LaFayette Ave. E.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"3830","name":"Greektown Casino - Bistro 555","address":"555 Lafayette Ave. E.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"3678","name":"Greektown Casino-Bars","address":"555 LaFayette Ave. E.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"3675","name":"Greektown Casino-Alley Grill","address":"555 LaFayette Ave. E.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"3452","name":"Lucky Green Vending","address":"555 Lafayette E.","zipcode":"49226"},{"establishmentid":"3833","name":"Greektown Casino-Opa Bar","address":"555 LaFayette Ave. E.","zipcode":"48226"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"62178","inspectionDate":"2023-04-12T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-201.11","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL shall be stored so they can not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES by:   \n(A) Separating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL by spacing or partitioning; (P) and   \n(B) Locating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL in an area that is not above FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.  This paragraph does not apply to EQUIPMENT and UTENSIL cleaners and sanitizers that are stored in WAREWASHING areas for availability and convenience if the materials are stored to prevent contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/with","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"On the Counter(s)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2023-04-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"On the Knife rack","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2023-04-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"60116","inspectionDate":"2022-08-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not accessible","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2022-08-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"On the Floor","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2022-08-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"On the Wall(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"58168","inspectionDate":"2022-03-31T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"57638","inspectionDate":"2022-03-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-101.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be safe, unADULTERATED and honestly presented. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Dishonestly presented","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"On the Shelves","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2022-03-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2022-03-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not accessible","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2022-03-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"At the Three compartment sink","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2022-03-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Pizza oven","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2022-03-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"56273","inspectionDate":"2021-10-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"On the Floor","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"54640","inspectionDate":"2021-04-12T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-102.11","violationDescription":"Working containers used for storing POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIALS such as cleaners and SANITIZERS taken from bulk supplies shall be clearly and individually identified with the common name of the material. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Working containers-toxics","subItem":"sanitizer","problemDescription":"Not labeled as to content","subProblem":"","location":"COFFEE STATION","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2021-04-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"53464","inspectionDate":"2020-10-29T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-402.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT that is fixed because it is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed so that it is spaced to allow access for cleaning along the sides, behind, and above the EQUIPMENT or sealed as required,  COUNTER-MOUNTED EQUIPMENT that is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed to allow cleaning of the EQUIPMENT and areas underneath and around the EQUIPMENT .\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Fixed equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to adjoining","subProblem":"Wall(s)","location":"VENTILATION HOOD SYSTEM","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"SIGNAGE","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-25T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51623314"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}